Let's see who dares to take me away. There's a Jiang family seed in my belly
This is your grandson. How could you bear to let her drift outside?
"Stop catching me here. At your age, how could you possibly get pregnant?"
This is a hospital. How could I lie? Your mom, your son is begging for a good year
I'm already crippled, but the child is the Jiang family's only heir
In my previous life, I transmigrated into the adultery between my husband and mother, and was killed
In this life, I will make your family pay for their blood debts
Xiao Lan, come quickly and help me wash my feet, Zhang Guifang
Don't go too far. Oh, my precious son said
He wanted his grandmother to personally serve him, but if he didn't do it well
He won't come out, just stay inside, watching who's anxious
Wife
Honey, calm down, be careful of the child in his belly
You're considering that our Jiang family is planting it in your belly. You should sweep it up. No, that's not right
This is really not right. Jiang Chengao's gaze was not the same as that of a daughter-in-law
Be gentle, I'm carrying your swelling in my belly, don't press on it